[{
		"id": 100,
		"title": "General",
		"clues_count": 20,
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1000,
				"answer": "Green",
				"question": "A term that describes a horse with very little training",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1001,
				"answer": "Bray",
				"question": "The sound a donkey makes",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1002,
				"answer": "Quick release",
				"question": "The type of knot used when tying up a horse",
				"value": 300,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1003,
				"answer": 32,
				"question": "Horses have this many pairs of chromosomes",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1004,
				"answer": "Ration",
				"question": "The entire feed allowed an animal during a 24 hour period",
				"value": 500,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1005,
				"answer": "Appointments",
				"question": "The term for clothing, tack, and equipment used in show riding",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1006,
				"answer": "Hippology",
				"question": "The term used for the study of the horse",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1007,
				"answer": "Get",
				"question": "The progeny of a stallion",
				"value": 600,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1008,
				"answer": "Grade",
				"question": "A term used for an unregistered horse of uncertain ancestry",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1009,
				"answer": "Hind",
				"question": "Which feet grow faster, hind or front",
				"value": 1000,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1010,
				"answer": "Sire",
				"question": "The gender of the foal is determined by this parent",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1011,
				"answer": "Cow hocked",
				"question": "A term for hocks that are closer together than normal",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1012,
				"answer": "TPR",
				"question": "An acronym for temperature, pulse, and respiration",
				"value": 600,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1013,
				"answer": "Blemish",
				"question": "A mark or deformity that is unattractive but does not affect a horse's usefulness",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1014,
				"answer": "Carrier",
				"question": "A term for an animal that can shed disease causing organisms",
				"value": 1000,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1015,
				"answer": "Unsoundness",
				"question": "A defect that affects the serviceability of a horse",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1016,
				"answer": "Gymkhana",
				"question": "A series of games on horseback",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1017,
				"answer": "Confirmation",
				"question": "A term used to describe the physical appearance of a animal due to the muscling, balance, and structural smoothness of a horse",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1018,
				"answer": "Farrier",
				"question": "A person that shoes horses",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1019,
				"answer": "Noseband",
				"question": "Another name for a cavesson",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1020,
				"answer": "10 gallons",
				"question": "The average dialy water intake of a mature 1000 pound horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1021,
				"answer": "Hard mouthed",
				"question": "A term that refers to a horse that is not responsive to the bit",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1022,
				"answer": "Tandem hitch",
				"question": "A term that describes a pair of horses hitched together one in front of the other when driving",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1023,
				"answer": "Cribbing",
				"question": "A term that describes biting or setting the teeth against an object while sucking in air",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 101,
		"title": "Breeds",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1024,
				"answer": "Falabella",
				"question": "A breed of horse developed by a family in Argentina",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 101,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1025,
				"answer": "Iowa",
				"question": "The American Cream Draft horse originated in this state",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 101,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1026,
				"answer": "Appaloosa",
				"question": "A breed developed by the Nez Perce Indians",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 101,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1027,
				"answer": "Clydesdale",
				"question": "A breed of large draught horse named after its area of origin in Scotland",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 101,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1028,
				"answer": "American Quarter Horse",
				"question": "The most popular breed of horse in America",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 101,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 102,
		"title": "Color",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1029,
				"answer": "Self colored",
				"question": "A horse that has a main and tail that are the same color as the body",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 102,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1030,
				"answer": "Skewbald",
				"question": "A term used to describe a paint or pinto horse that has white on any base coat color other than black",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 102,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1031,
				"answer": "Bay",
				"question": "A horse with a brown body, black manes and tails, and points on the legs, faces, and ears",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 102,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1032,
				"answer": "Dun",
				"question": "Horses of this type can be a variety of shades, but usually have a dorsal stripe",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 102,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1033,
				"answer": "Palomino",
				"question": "A horse with a golden coat and creamy white manes and tails",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 102,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 103,
		"title": "Development",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1034,
				"answer": "fetus",
				"question": "An unborn baby horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1035,
				"answer": "Milk Teeth",
				"question": "The name of the temporary teeth of a foal",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1036,
				"answer": "Filly",
				"question": "A female horse under 3 years of age.",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1037,
				"answer": "Colostrum",
				"question": "The name of the mare's first milk",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1038,
				"answer": "11 months",
				"question": "The length of time for the gestation of a horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 104,
		"title": "Anatomy",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1039,
				"answer": "Bladder",
				"question": "A stretchable, membranous sac that temporarily holds urine secreted by the kidneys",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 103,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1040,
				"answer": "Uterus",
				"question": "The internal organ where the unborn fetus is developed",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 104,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1041,
				"answer": "Mandible",
				"question": "The name for the lower jawbone",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 104,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1042,
				"answer": "Navicular bone",
				"question": "The small, flat bone that lies within the hoof",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 104,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1043,
				"answer": "Ankle",
				"question": "Another name for the fetlock joint",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 104,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1044,
				"answer": 7,
				"question": "The number of cervical vertebrae in a horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 104,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 105,
		"title": "Medical",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1045,
				"answer": "Cushing's disease",
				"question": "A disease caused by a tumor on the pituatary gland",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 105,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1046,
				"answer": "Vitamin K",
				"question": "The vitamin essential to aid in blood clotting",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 105,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1047,
				"answer": "Colic",
				"question": "The general term for pain in the abdomen",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 105,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1048,
				"answer": 100,
				"question": "The average temperature of a horse in degrees",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 105,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1049,
				"answer": "Chestnut",
				"question": "A term that describes a horny growth on the inside of a horse's leg",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 105,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	},{
		"id": 106,
		"title": "Movement",
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1050,
				"answer": "Pace",
				"question": "A 2 beat, lateral gait",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 106,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1051,
				"answer": 3,
				"question": "The number of beats in a canter",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 106,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1052,
				"answer": 4,
				"question": "The number of beats in a gallop",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 106,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1053,
				"answer": 1,
				"question": "The number of beats in a walk",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 106,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1054,
				"answer": 2,
				"question": "The number of beats in a trot",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 106,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
	}
]